I'll go then.
Hakeyoyo.
Remaining.
One.
Don't you mean, "One more try"?
Oh, I'm being nice.
I'm being nice?
I'm being nice.
I didn't lose.
I lost.
That much?
I'm so happy.
Good riddance.
We're in.
Wow.
Ten.
Woohoo.
Wait.
Weak.
Wait, weak.
You're good. You're good.
Chan chan.
Face.
You have a face that can't be shown to the world.
So, you won!
Congratulations.
100 kilos.100 kilometers.
Do this again.
Do it this way.
Oh, 30 kilometers.
Ah, 30 kilos.
Very weak. Very weak.
Very weak.
I won't lose.
I can go, I can go!
Go, go, go.
Wait.
Wow.
Yay.
All right.
We did it.
He's strong. I won! Strong.
This is a loss, right? In our house? Oh, it's strong!
I won.
So, lastly, because I forgot to beat the last boss,
I'd like to defeat the boss for the last time.
Kojima-san, I'm counting on you.
Frison is the last one, because after he's taken, everyone else will lose.
The popular Chandarak won't be able to take it.
I'm back, I'm back.
I'll do my best.
I'm out of rice.
The Czechs are out.
I'm so screwed!
by H. aaiassy
aaiassyaaiassy
aaiassy aaiassy aaiassy aaiassy aaiassy aaiassy aaiassy aaiassy aaiassy aaiassy
ni
goo Then I'll really rephrase it, Datz.
kanai kushi voice
Kayla no way Tokyo media
one
Oh no!
Oh, no!
No! No! No!
No! No! No! No! No!
Go! Go! Go!
I forgot, Mum!
I forgot, Momma!
Go! Let's go!
Let's go!
No! Oh, shit!
Ugh! Uy!
Uy! Uy! Uy!
What the hell!
Unh!
Whoo!
Yeah! Yeah! Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
Oh, no, over here.
I got an eight.
What? Ali?What's that? Ants?
Okay, so you're an ant and a kangaroo.
Oh, my God, that's good.
That's good, too.
Not in a paradisiacal way.
I told her I'd play with Hana-chan.
Ali won.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Good luck losing to Ali.
I'm having so much fun!
I'm having fun.
Well, you didn't have to go out.
That's great.
No, no, no, it's fine.
Oh, you can do it.
Why not?
What about you, Mr. Kaukomi?
Can I do it?
What are you doing?
If you win, Mr. Koukomi...
If you win, we can call it even.
Are you sure?
What are you going to do?
Do it.
We'll do it.
Don't you get it?
Sumo wrestling, please.
It's two-handed wrestling.
You can throw it. It's okay to throw it.
I kinda don't get it.
Hell.
Hell?
I don't know what to do.
Now, let's wrestle Kaukomi-san and Rouge-no-Hana.
Win!
Remaining.
Oh, what? What?
What's this?
I like Mr. Kaukomi.
He's not even winning.
Change your face.
Excuse me, Rector.
What was the right answer?
You look disappointed.
That's why you were all up in the air.
You lost.
I'll see you later.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, I'm busy.
Thank you.
Why are you doing this?
I have no idea.
I knew it... Kurokuro-san...
Kaukomi, the wall is still there.
Let's try again.I knew it. Why don't we try again?
I want to come back.
She wants to come back.
I can't tell by the look on your face.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna extend this.
They're close.
Yeah, they're close.
Just keep complimenting them.
That's good. That's good.
Oh, my God. PPP.
Force close, force close.
Hana, you lose.
Hana, lose.
Kikkiss.
First
Nose scratch
Touch
Now thud
Throb
That's a honeymoon.
Plenty of room.
Wait a minute.
I'm scared.
I'm scared.I'm scared.
I don't know.
I don't know. I mean, it's not like we're going to win.
Five.
Four.
We lose.
Kocchan is the cutest.
He's a little...
He's quite a little fellow.
Look, look, look.
On the screen...
You!
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Here we go.
Stavran
Start
Thank you
Thank you very much.